{
    "general_knowledge": {
      "id": "691f3aad-8ad2-413d-8222-0fe6c1a52be3",
      "description": "A wide range of information that encompasses various subjects, including history, politics, literature, and culture related to Ireland.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id":  "68fe2b01-b4fe-44fb-87f3-f97621bd4c71",
          "question": "What is the capital of Ireland?",
          "answer": "Dublin",
          "options": [
            "Dublin",
            "Cork",
            "Galway",
            "Limerick",
            "Belfast",
            "Waterford",
            "Derry",
            "Kilkenny"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "c1697647-5837-497a-a55d-a930a0cebc36",
          "question": "What is the national symbol of Ireland?",
          "answer": "Shamrock",
          "options": [
            "Shamrock",
            "Harp",
            "Claddagh ring",
            "Celtic cross",
            "Trinity knot",
            "Irish wolfhound",
            "Leprechaun",
            "Potato"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "5fc696f3-42af-4915-ab01-d60fbb410fd4",
          "question": "What is the name of the river that flows through Dublin?",
          "answer": "Liffey",
          "options": [
            "Liffey",
            "Shannon",
            "Lee",
            "Boyne",
            "Barrow",
            "Blackwater",
            "Nore",
            "Suir"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "9f508a17-1de0-4bb3-8c1a-e19260610008",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous prison in Dublin?",
          "answer": "Kilmainham Gaol",
          "options": [
            "Kilmainham Gaol",
            "Mountjoy Prison",
            "Wheatfield Prison",
            "Cloverhill Prison",
            "Arbour Hill Prison",
            "Castlerea Prison",
            "Loughan House",
            "Portlaoise Prison"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "4eabe612-7861-4abd-9c7f-0bfd67c25f97",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish beer?",
          "answer": "Guinness",
          "options": [
            "Guinness",
            "Smithwick's",
            "Harp",
            "Kilkenny",
            "Beamish",
            "Murphy's",
            "Bulmers",
            "Magners"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "81f3fd42-f059-4734-9716-2bc15bd736d0",
          "question": "What is the name of the Irish language?",
          "answer": "Gaeilge",
          "options": [
            "Gaeilge",
            "Gaelic",
            "Irish",
            "Celtic",
            "Scots",
            "Welsh",
            "Breton",
            "Manx"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "10cc3bbb-0908-4cdb-a456-fc6858be6609",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish rock band?",
          "answer": "U2",
          "options": [
            "U2",
            "Thin Lizzy",
            "The Cranberries",
            "The Pogues",
            "The Dubliners",
            "The Chieftains",
            "Sinead O'Connor",
            "Van Morrison"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "54b87b6f-eaa2-4f68-910a-8f2beaa13d41",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish playwright and poet?",
          "answer": "William Butler Yeats",
          "options": [
            "William Butler Yeats",
            "Oscar Wilde",
            "George Bernard Shaw",
            "Samuel Beckett",
            "Seamus Heaney",
            "James Joyce",
            "Brendan Behan",
            "Patrick Kavanagh"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "37b456cb-8793-4f3a-84fd-a9397ff989ff",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish holiday celebrated on March ?",
          "answer": "St. Patrick's Day",
          "options": [
            "St. Patrick's Day",
            "Easter",
            "Christmas",
            "Halloween",
            "New Year's Day",
            "Valentine's Day",
            "Mother's Day",
            "Father's Day"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id":  "1dd419985-485d-42ba-bbc2-647eb83628b9",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish castle that is now a museum?",
          "answer": "Blarney Castle",
          "options": [
            "Blarney Castle",
            "Dublin Castle",
            "Kilkenny Castle",
            "Bunratty Castle",
            "Malahide Castle",
            "Cahir Castle",
            "Rock of Cashel",
            "Trim Castle"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "geography": {
      "id": "c7db0fb3-9fa9-4df9-b96c-71f675d0f94c",
      "description": "The physical features, landmarks, and regions of Ireland, including its rugged coastline, rolling hills, ancient monuments, and bustling cities like Dublin, Cork, and Galway.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": "1b281627d-cc0a-4529-9dc1-cda991420a02",
          "question": "What is the highest mountain in Ireland?",
          "answer": "Carrauntoohil",
          "options": [
            "Carrauntoohil",
            "Mount Brandon",
            "Mweelrea",
            "Dingle Peninsula",
            "Slieve Donard",
            "Ben Nevis",
            "Snowdon",
            "Scafell Pike"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "15ebc1a87-1721-4d4f-bb73-55b6d6f2fedc",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous sea cliffs located in County Clare?",
          "answer": "Cliffs of Moher",
          "options": [
            "Cliffs of Moher",
            "Ring of Kerry",
            "Giant's Causeway",
            "Dingle Peninsula",
            "Slea Head",
            "Connemara",
            "Aran Islands",
            "Skellig Michael"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1ca510bf3-aa12-4f34-bc64-fb4ce0dd5cd9",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish river that forms the border between Northern Ireland and the Republic of Ireland?",
          "answer": "River Foyle",
          "options": [
            "River Foyle",
            "River Shannon",
            "River Liffey",
            "River Boyne",
            "River Barrow",
            "River Corrib",
            "River Blackwater",
            "River Nore"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1f2be5709-1714-4ba1-9355-2a12fea8a3af",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish lake that inspired many poets and writers?",
          "answer": "Lough Derg",
          "options": [
            "Lough Derg",
            "Lough Neagh",
            "Lough Corrib",
            "Lough Erne",
            "Lough Ree",
            "Lough Conn",
            "Lough Mask",
            "Lough Swilly"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1580e5d36-377a-4404-8ea0-f9fdc3fe0aea",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish peninsula known for its rugged beauty?",
          "answer": "Dingle Peninsula",
          "options": [
            "Dingle Peninsula",
            "Ring of Kerry",
            "Beara Peninsula",
            "Inishowen Peninsula",
            "Connemara",
            "Sheep's Head",
            "Mizen Head",
            "Slea Head"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "168fe1a03-b71d-4a58-b595-39ca8c6c8319",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish island known for its pilgrimage site?",
          "answer": "Skellig Michael",
          "options": [
            "Skellig Michael",
            "Croagh Patrick",
            "Aran Islands",
            "Inishbofin",
            "Inishturk",
            "Clare Island",
            "Rathlin Island",
            "Arranmore Island"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1cc5c546f-450d-4540-8bce-514689ad07d9",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish mountain range located in the west of Ireland?",
          "answer": "Connemara Mountains",
          "options": [
            "Connemara Mountains",
            "Macgillycuddy's Reeks",
            "Wicklow Mountains",
            "Mourne Mountains",
            "Cuilcagh Mountains",
            "Comeragh Mountains",
            "Slieve Bloom Mountains",
            "Sperrin Mountains"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "1e35bbfea-dbd7-4c22-b99f-aec514c7b00e",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish beach known for its surf?",
          "answer": "Bundoran Beach",
          "options": [
            "Bundoran Beach",
            "Inch Beach",
            "Rossbeigh Beach",
            "Clogherhead Beach",
            "Brittas Bay",
            "Tramore Beach",
            "Strandhill Beach",
            "Curracloe Beach"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "244023e8d-a6b7-4b45-9439-8a84958a6e27",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish forest located in County Wicklow?",
          "answer": "Glendalough Forest",
          "options": [
            "Glendalough Forest",
            "Killarney National Park",
            "Glenveagh National Park",
            "Coole Park",
            "Powerscourt Estate",
            "Doneraile Park",
            "Phoenix Park",
            "Fota Wildlife Park"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2d7468fad-7357-4862-b72c-7706b4fc9b5e",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish golf course located in County Kerry?",
          "answer": "Ballybunion Golf Club",
          "options": [
            "Ballybunion Golf Club",
            "Royal Portrush Golf Club",
            "Portmarnock Golf Club",
            "The K Club",
            "Lahinch Golf Club",
            "Druid's Glen Golf Club",
            "Mount Juliet Golf Club",
            "Old Head Golf Links"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "food": {
      "id": "25e8caf7-2583-490f-81e5-20cd54f43398",
      "description": "Traditional Irish cuisine, which includes dishes such as Irish stew, boxty, soda bread, and colcannon, as well as popular Irish beverages like Guinness and whiskey.",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": "28160b014-5930-4579-b0f0-73caa385fbad",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish stew?",
          "answer": "Irish stew",
          "options": [
            "Irish stew",
            "Shepherd's pie",
            "Corned beef and cabbage",
            "Fish and chips",
            "Bangers and mash",
            "Beef and Guinness pie",
            "Boxty",
            "Colcannon"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2d62f2332-caa1-40bd-a102-6ac2d0496fde",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish bread?",
          "answer": "Soda bread",
          "options": [
            "Soda bread",
            "Brown bread",
            "White bread",
            "Rye bread",
            "Baguette",
            "Ciabatta",
            "Focaccia",
            "Pita bread"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "26378ab9c-2021-47a4-bc85-0a3b7562eacf",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish cheese?",
          "answer": "Cashel Blue",
          "options": [
            "Cashel Blue",
            "Dubliner",
            "Blarney Castle",
            "Cooleeney",
            "Durrus",
            "Gubbeen",
            "Ardsallagh",
            "Carrigaline"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2d46cea3a-438a-4b40-99c1-1e7181cb70ba",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish dessert?",
          "answer": "Baileys cheesecake",
          "options": [
            "Baileys cheesecake",
            "Apple pie",
            "Bread and butter pudding",
            "Eton mess",
            "Sticky toffee pudding",
            "Lemon tart",
            "Chocolate cake",
            "Carrot cake"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2cee25870-efde-4e74-abdd-a7f22e6f88b5",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish sausage?",
          "answer": "Black pudding",
          "options": [
            "Black pudding",
            "White pudding",
            "Boudin noir",
            "Chorizo",
            "Andouille",
            "Merguez",
            "Bratwurst",
            "Kielbasa"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2df1e651b-4bba-4a37-9674-007e0331e4fd",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish whiskey?",
          "answer": "Jameson",
          "options": [
            "Jameson",
            "Bushmills",
            "Tullamore Dew",
            "Powers",
            "Redbreast",
            "Green Spot",
            "Yellow Spot",
            "Midleton Very Rare"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2f11eef29-59ec-4537-8cc4-41c423b48feb",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish beer?",
          "answer": "Guinness",
          "options": [
            "Guinness",
            "Smithwick's",
            "Harp",
            "Kilkenny",
            "Beamish",
            "Murphy's",
            "Bulmers",
            "Magners"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "2da6a4cc4-420e-4fb8-8985-d05548109c04",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish coffee?",
          "answer": "Irish coffee",
          "options": [
            "Irish coffee",
            "Cappuccino",
            "Latte",
            "Espresso",
            "Mocha",
            "Americano",
            "Flat white",
            "Macchiato"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "386e171dd-cb55-49ef-a6ae-60e5c124d83f",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish potato dish?",
          "answer": "Colcannon",
          "options": [
            "Colcannon",
            "Champ",
            "Boxty",
            "Bubble and squeak",
            "Potato gratin",
            "Potato dauphinoise",
            "Potato croquettes",
            "Potato pancakes"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "3cecf7459-4e02-4282-a654-3d77f70b4f14",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish seafood dish?",
          "answer": "Fish and chips",
          "options": [
            "Fish and chips",
            "Seafood chowder",
            "Smoked salmon",
            "Oysters",
            "Mussels",
            "Clams",
            "Prawns",
            "Crab claws"
          ]
        }
      ]
    },
    "culture": {
      "id": "79ab9dee-16cc-4634-bcb2-383043d8de39",
      "description": "The rich and diverse cultural heritage of Ireland, including its music, dance, literature, folklore, and language (Gaeilge).",
      "questions": [
        {
          "id": "33f964f18-5cc5-4c7b-861a-cac33c9f9262",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish dance?",
          "answer": "Riverdance",
          "options": [
            "Riverdance",
            "Jig",
            "Reel",
            "Hornpipe",
            "Set dance",
            "Step dance",
            "Ceili dance",
            "Waltz"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "30a55bc56-8a5d-434e-9bf2-10960cbef00f",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish festival celebrating the start of summer?",
          "answer": "Bealtaine",
          "options": [
            "Bealtaine",
            "Samhain",
            "Lughnasadh",
            "Imbolc",
            "St. Patrick's Day",
            "Bloomsday",
            "Galway Arts Festival",
            "Cork Jazz Festival"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "3c158cdc1-019a-4bfb-baf4-8581519d97e9",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish poet who wrote 'The Waste Land'?",
          "answer": "T.S. Eliot",
          "options": [
            "T.S. Eliot",
            "W.B. Yeats",
            "Seamus Heaney",
            "Patrick Kavanagh",
            "Eavan Boland",
            "Paul Muldoon",
            "Derek Mahon",
            "Michael Longley"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "33049afa4-43e4-4588-b867-685cf034b645",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish folk tale about a mischievous creature?",
          "answer": "The leprechaun",
          "options": [
            "The leprechaun",
            "The banshee",
            "The pooka",
            "The selkie",
            "The merrow",
            "The sidhe",
            "The kelpie",
            "The changeling"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "32a555ad3-889e-4736-a793-49f6ba418754",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish language poet who wrote 'Cúirt an Mhéan Oíche'?",
          "answer": "Brian Merriman",
          "options": [
            "Brian Merriman",
            "Aodhagán Ó Rathaille",
            "Máire Mhac an tSaoi",
            "Nuala Ní Dhomhnaill",
            "Ciarán Carson",
            "Michael Hartnett",
            "Seán Ó Ríordáin",
            "Micheál Ó Siadhail"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "31f5436eb-04ad-4851-8e8e-110d9c5d2b91",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish mythological hero who defeated the sea serpent?",
          "answer": "Fionn mac Cumhaill",
          "options": [
            "Fionn mac Cumhaill",
            "Cúchulainn",
            "Diarmuid Ua Duibhne",
            "Oisín",
            "Cormac mac Airt",
            "Niall of the Nine Hostages",
            "Bran mac Febail",
            "Lugh"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "3346d85d8-24e2-475c-9c07-f36d6ec403be",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish author who wrote 'Ulysses'?",
          "answer": "James Joyce",
          "options": [
            "James Joyce",
            "Samuel Beckett",
            "Oscar Wilde",
            "George Bernard Shaw",
            "Brendan Behan",
            "Flann O'Brien",
            "Frank McCourt",
            "Roddy Doyle"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "39f81ddb0-693a-4c4a-8988-ccdbd23cb647",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish actor who played James Bond?",
          "answer": "Pierce Brosnan",
          "options": [
            "Pierce Brosnan",
            "Daniel Craig",
            "Sean Connery",
            "Roger Moore",
            "Timothy Dalton",
            "George Lazenby",
            "David Niven",
            "Barry Nelson"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "45b209369-ecac-46bf-83aa-bed0f80a511d",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish musician who played the lead guitar for U2?",
          "answer": "The Edge",
          "options": [
            "The Edge",
            "Bono",
            "Adam Clayton",
            "Larry Mullen Jr.",
            "Van Morrison",
            "Sinead O'Connor",
            "Christy Moore",
            "Enya"
          ]
        },
        {
          "id": "4e28dde9d-180b-4ff2-b77e-aeed5b56c040",
          "question": "What is the name of the famous Irish actor who played Batman?",
          "answer": "Michael Keaton",
          "options": [
            "Michael Keaton",
            "Christian Bale",
            "Ben Affleck",
            "Val Kilmer",
            "George Clooney",
            "Liam Neeson",
            "Pierce Brosnan",
            "Daniel Day-Lewis"
          ]
        }
      ]
    }
  }
  